Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 3 and District 3 Locals, 1936-1990s UE.4.1.3
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 3, 1.
  - District 3 Outgoing Leo Jandreau Correspondence, January 7-November 25, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding District 3 Convention, September 11, 1946; 15.
    - Jandreau to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding District 3 Convention, September 11, 1946; 16.
    - Jandreau to Matles Regarding District 3 Convention, September 11, 1946; 17.
    - Jandreau to Barish Regarding Staff Finances, October 15-30, 1946; 18-19.
    - Jandreau to Ray Klausner Regarding District 3 Officers, November 12, 1946; 20.
    - Jandreau to David Ratner Regarding Finances with November 15, 1946, Jandreau Letter to Ratner, November 25, 1946; 21.
  - District 3 Outgoing Leo Jandreau Correspondence, December 10, 1946-December 1, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Leo Jandreau to Janet Barish Regarding Staff Finances, December 10, 1946; 1.
    - Jandreau to David Ratner Regarding Finances, December 24, 1946; 2.
    - Jandreau to UE Regarding Political Action Committee, January 8, 1947; 3.
    - Jandreau to UE Regarding District 3 Officers, January 28, 1947; 4.
    - Jandreau to Julius Emspak Regarding Address Change, February 11, 1947; 5.
    - Jandreau to Ratner Regarding Address Change, March 31, 1947; 6.
    - Jandreau Telegram to Emspak Regarding Finances, April 18, 1947; 7.
    - Jandreau to Barish Regarding Staff Finances, April 22, 1947; 8.
    - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee with Receipts, April 25, 1947; 9.
    - Jandreau Telegram to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding General Electric Contracts, April 28-29, 1947; 10-11.
    - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Committee for Democrtaic Action with Jandreau Letter to All District 3 Locals, May 2, 1947; 12.
    - Jandreau to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Wages and Factionalism, May 5, 1947; 13.
    - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Constitutions and Finances, May 19, 1947; 14.
    - Jandreau to Barish Regarding Staff Finances, May 27, 1947; 15.
    - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Stewards, June 17, 1947; 16.
    - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, June 24, 1947; 17.
    - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Religion and Labor Foundation with November 26, 1947, Willard Ophavs Letter to Jandreau and "Call to the National Religion and Labor Conference", December 1, 1947; 18.
  - District 3 Outgoing Leo Jandreau Correspondence, January 7, 1948-March 25, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Leo Jandreau to James Matles Regarding Supplies, January 7, 1948; 1.
    - Jandreau to Janet Barish Regarding Publicity, March 10, 1948; 2.
    - Jandreau to William Cahn Regarding Publicity, March 10, 1948; 3.
    - Jandreau to Julius Emspak Regarding Locals 304 and 305, Finances and Jamestown Sylvania Runaway Shops, September 15, 1948; 4.
    - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Stewards, September 15, 1948; 5.
    - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding District 3 Convention with Convention Call, September 20, 1948; 6.
    - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Local 1581 and Per Capita with Jandreau Letter to Theodore Wierzbic, September 21, 1948; 7.
    - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding District Council Meeting, March 28, 1949; 8.
    - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Finances, October 25, 1950; 9.
    - Jandreau Telegram to James Matles Regarding Local 301 General Electric Collective Bargaining, February 14, 1952; 10.
    - Jandreau Telegram to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Local 301 and Shop Stewards Meeting, March 25, 1952; 11.
    - Jandreau Telegram to Emspak Regarding Local 301 and Shop Stewards Meeting, March 25, 1952; 12.
    - Jandreau Telegram to Matles Regarding Local 301 and Shop Stewards Meeting, March 25, 1952; 13.
  - District 3 Incoming Lewis King Correspondence, November 14, 1950-January 10, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Janet Barish Regarding Address List, June 18, 1952; 1.
    - Julius Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, November 14, 1950; 2.
    - Emspak Regarding Supplies, January 15, 1951; 3.
    - Emspak Telegram Regarding Supplies, February 8, 1951; 4.
    - Emspak Regarding Political Action, March 12, 1951; 5.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 309 and Per Capita, March 26, 1951; 6.
    - Emspak Regarding High Treason, April 23, 1951; 7.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, April 24, 1951; 8.
    - Emspak Regarding High Treason, April 27, 1951; 9.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 309 and Finances, May 7, 1951; 10.
    - Emspak Regarding Political Action, May 16, 1951; 11.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, May 28, 1951; 12.
    - Emspak Regarding Voting Strength, October 17, 1951; 13.
    - Emspak Telegram, October 22, 1951; 14.
    - Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, November 9, 1951; 15.
    - Emspak Regarding Jamestown and Buffalo, February 19, 1952; 16.
    - Emspak Regarding District Council Meeting, July 22, 1953; 17.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 331 and Per Capita, November 18, 1953; 18.
    - Emspak Regarding Locals 331 and 333, and Per Capita, May 8, 1954; 19.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 301 and Finances, November 5, 1954; 20.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 326 and Arbitration with November 13, 1954, Herman Barnes Letter to UE, November 15, 1954; 21.
    - Emspak Regarding Mill Town, December 13, 1954; 22.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 301 and Finances, January 10, 1955; 23.
  - District 3 Incoming Lewis King Correspondence, December 17, 1950-May 1, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Julius Emspak Regarding Local 326 and Finances with January 10, 1955, Letter to UE, January 4, 1955; 1.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 301 and Finances, February 23-April 28, 1955; 2-5.
    - Emspak Regarding District 3 and Westinghouse Strikes, March 2, 1956; 6.
    - Emspak Regarding UE News and International Association of Machinists with District 3 UE News Stories, May 1, 1956; 7.
    - Albert Fitzgerald, March 25, 1954; 8.
    - James Matles Regarding Staff Finances, December 17, 1950; 9.
    - Emspak Regarding Wages and Political Action, January 8, 1951; 10.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, January 10, 1951; 11.
    - Matles Regarding A. S. Campbell, Chrysler Air Temp and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, March 23, 1951; 12.
    - Matles Regarding Local 302, April 3, 1951; 13.
    - Matles Regarding Watsop, Inter-union Rivalry and Dahlstrom Strikes, July 13, 1951; 14.
    - Matles Regarding Buffalo Westinghouse, July 24, 1951; 15.
    - Matles Regarding Louis Budenz, October 22, 1951; 16.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, October 29, 1951; 17.
  - District 3 Incoming Lewis King Correspondence, January 15, 1952-December 22, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - James Matles Regarding Staff Members and Auburn General Electric, January 15, 1952; 1.
    - Matles Regarding Political Action and Staff Members, April 4, 1952; 2.
    - Matles Regarding Supplies, November 6, 1952; 3.
    - Matles Regarding Political Action and Finances, December 5, 1952; 4.
    - Matles Regarding Finances and Political Action, December 22, 1956; 5.
    - Matles Regarding Lynn General Electric, August 20, 1953; 6.
    - Matles Regarding Mica Strikes, November 29, 1954; 7.
  - District 3 Outgoing Lewis King Correspondence, March 19, 1950-February 21, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Lewis King to Janet Barish Regarding Finances, March 19, 1950; 1.
    - King to Julius Emspak Regarding Staff Members, November 6, 1950; 2.
    - King to James Matles Regarding Staff Finances, December 14, 1950; 3.
    - King to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Defense Fund, January 3, 1951; 4.
    - King to James Matles Regarding Supplies, January 3, 1951; 5.
    - King to Matles Regarding Local 307 Dahlstrom Collective Bargaining and Wages, January 28, 1951; 6.
    - King to Barish, February 7, 1951; 7.
    - King to Emspak Regarding Local 309, Finances and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, February 7, 1951; 8.
    - King to Emspak Regarding Local 309 and Finances, February 22, 1951; 9.
    - King to Matles Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, A. S. Campbell and Frigadaire, March 19, 1951; 10.
    - King to Matles Regarding Local 302 and Finances, March 31, 1951; 11.
    - King to Emspak Regarding Local 309 and Per Capita, April 2, 1951; 12.
    - King to David Ratner Regarding Finances, April 19, 1951; 13.
    - King to Peter Breier Regarding Finances, May 31, 1951; 14.
    - King to Paul Baum Regarding Finances, May 31, 1951; 15.
    - King to Charles Pattison Regarding Local 309 and Finances, June 6, 1951; 16.
    - King to Ratner Regarding Finances, September 29, 1951; 17.
    - King to Emspak Regarding Per Capita and District Council Meeting, October 13, 1951; 18.
    - King to Emspak Regarding Figting Fund, October 17, 1951; 19.
    - King to Matles Regarding Louis Budenz, Local 307 Dahlstrom Strikes and IUE, International Association of Machinists and United Steelworkers of America Inter-union Rivalry, October 19, 1951; 20.
    - King to Fitzgerald, December 19, 1951; 21.
    - King to Matles Regarding Staff Members, December 27, 1951; 22.
    - King Telegram to Emspak, February 15, 1952; 23.
    - King Telegram to Sylvia Cohen Regarding Local 301, February 20, 1952; 24.
    - King to Emspak Regarding UE Fighting Fund, February 21, 1952; 25.
  - District 3 Outgoing Lewis King Correspondence, March 1952-October 1955 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Lewis King to James Matles Regarding Staff Members and Jamestown Organization, March 12, 1952; 1.
    - King to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding District Council Meeting, July 1, 1952; 2.
    - King to Julius Emspak Regarding Local 302 and Dues, July 11, 1952; 3.
    - King to Fitzgerald Regarding Staff Meeting, January 2, 1953; 4.
    - King to Matles with King Telegram to Stanley Sanscrainte, February 9, 1953; 5.
    - King Telegram to Matles Regarding Staff Meeting, February 16, 1953; 6.
    - King to Emspak Regarding District Council Meeting, July 17, 1953; 7.
    - King Telegram to Fitzgerald, December 30, 1953; 8.
    - King Telegram to Neal Eastman Regarding Staff Meeting, January 4, 1954; 9.
    - King to Elmer Johnson Regarding Local 307 and Finances, January 28, 1954; 10.
    - King to William Sampson Regarding Local 305 and Finances, January 28, 1954; 11.
    - King to Alwin Holcomb Regarding 1954 UE Convention, August 9, 1954; 12.
    - King to David Ratner Regarding Finances, October 2, 1954; 13.
    - King to Emspak Regarding Local 301 and Per Capita, October 6, 1954; 14.
    - King to Emspak Regarding Local 305 and Finances, January 7, 1955; 15.
    - King to Fitzgerald Regarding Local 301 and Finances, February 8, 1955; 16.
    - King to Governor Craig Regarding Perfict Circle Strikes, October 1955; 17.
    - King to Dwight Eisenhower Regarding Matles Case with District 3 Letter to Herbert Brownell, October 1955; 18.
    - King to Robert Nellis Regarding IUE and Westinghouse Collective Bargaining, October 1955; 19.
    - King to United Auto Workers Regarding UAW Perfect Circle Strikes, October 1955; 20.
  - District 3 Outgoing Lewis King Correspondence, January 26-April 23, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Lewis King to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism, January 26, 1956; 1.
    - King to Fitzgerald Regarding International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry with June 30, 1956, E. R. White Letter to King, February 1, 1956; 2.
    - King Telegram to White Regarding International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, February 1956; 3.
    - King to Julius Emspak Regarding Westinghouse Strikes, March 30, 1956; 4.
    - King to Fitzgerald Regarding UE News and IAM Inter-union Rivalry, April 23, 1956; 5.
  - District 3 Incoming Charles Rivers Correspondence, March 2, 1948-June 28, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Janet Barish Regarding Finances, May 25, 1949; 1.
    - Barish Regarding Staff Finances, August 26, 1949; 2.
    - William Cahn, March 9, 1949; 3.
    - Cahn Regarding District Council Meetings, June 27, 1949; 4.
    - Cahn Regarding Publicity, January 6, 1950; 5.
    - Fred d'Avila Regarding New York Consumer Council, February 16, 1949; 6.
    - d'Avila Regarding Health Care, April 29, 1949; 7.
    - Julius Emspak Regarding District Council Meeting, June 5, 1950; 8.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, June 28, 1950; 9.
    - Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations and Factionalism, March 2, 1948; 10.
    - Fitzgerald Regarding Local 317, February 8, 1950; 11.
    - James Matles Telegram, June 3, 1949; 12.
    - Matles Regarding District Council Meeting, June 24, 1949; 13.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Finances, July 7, 1949; 14.
    - Matles Telegram Regarding 1949 UE Convention, August 9, 1949; 15.
    - Matles Regarding Local 322 Constitutions, January 19, 150; 16.
    - Matles Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, January 28, 1950; 17.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Finances, February 24-March 25, 1950; 18-20.
    - David Ratner Regarding Finances, February 9-18, 1949; 21-22.
    - Ratner Regarding Staff Finances, May 31, 1950; 23.
  - District 3 Outgoing Charles Rivers Correspondence, March 7, 1947-July 1, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Charles Rivers to Julius Emspak Regarding Address Change, March 7, 1947; 1.
    - Rivers to James Matles Regarding Staff Members with District 3 Staff Assignments, August 6, 1947; 2.
    - Rivers to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Political Action with Leo Jandreau Statement, January 23, 1948; 3.
    - Rivers to Matles Regarding Staff Members, May 5, 1948; 4.
    - Rivers to Matles Regarding Taft-Hartley and Political Action with Jandreau Letter to All Locals and "Beat Back the Union Bosters" Leaflet, September 21, 1948; 5.
    - Rivers to David Ratner Regarding Finances, October 22, 1948; 6.
    - Rivers to Matles Regarding United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry, Tonawanda Rem-Rand and Buffalo Bolt, January 11, 1949; 7.
    - Rivers to Ratner Regarding Staff Finances, February 2, 1949; 8.
    - Rivers to Ratner Regarding United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry and 1948 UE Convention, February 14, 1949; 9.
    - Rivers to Nat Spero Regarding Health Care, April 27, 1949; 10.
    - Rivers to Emspak Regarding Finances, May 24, 1949; 11.
    - Rivers to William Cahn Regarding Wages and Publicity, June 22, 1949; 12.
    - Rivers to Matles Regarding District Council Meeting with Leo Jandreau Letter to All Locals, June 22, 1949; 13.
    - Rivers to Matles Regarding Factionalism, Association of Catholic Trade Unionists, and Staff Members, July 1, 1949; 14.
    - Rivers to Matles Regarding Local 320 and Factionalism with June 7, 1949, Leo Jandreau Letter to Mark Clancy and June 14, 1949, James Monroe to Jandreau, July 1, 1949; 15.
  - District 3 Outgoing Charles Rivers Correspondence, October 14, 1949-June 27, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Charles Rivers to Julius Emspak Regarding District Three Convention, October 14, 1949; 1.
    - Rivers to Janet Barish Regarding Finances, October 17, 1949; 2.
    - Rivers to James Matles Regarding Supplies, October 21, 1949; 3.
    - Rivers to Janet Barish, November 4, 1949; 4.
    - Rivers to Barish Regarding Staff Finances, December 9, 1949; 5.
    - Rivers to Emspak Regarding District Council Meeting, January 4, 1950; 6.
    - Rivers to Emspak Regarding Finances, February 6, 1950; 7.
    - Rivers to Matles Regarding Staff Finances, February 20, 1950; 8.
    - Rivers to Emspak Regarding Local 332 and Per Capita, February 27, 1950; 9.
    - Rivers to Matles Regarding Staff Finances, February 27-March 26, 1950; 10-11.
    - Rivers to Matles Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, May 4, 1950; 12.
    - Rivers to Emspak Regarding District Council Meeting, May 29, 1950; 13.
    - Rivers to Emspak Regarding Finances, May 29, 1950; 14.
    - Rivers to Emspak Regarding Local 1107 and Finances, June 27, 1950; 15.
  - District 3 Incoming Correspondence, April 7, 1937-April 3, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Janet Barish to Roy Lash Regarding Finances, February 28, 1945; 1.
    - Barish to John Baston Regarding Staff Finances, December 7, 1945; 2.
    - Barish to Morea Ganross Regarding Staff Finances, January 8-February 19, 1946; 3-4.
    - Barish to Baston Regarding Staff Finances, August 19, 1946; 5.
    - Barish to Genevieve Winaiski Regarding Staff Finances, February 20, 1947; 6.
    - Barish to Katherine Hull Regarding Staff Finances, February 28, 1950; 7.
    - Barish to Harold Buck Regarding Staff Finances, April 3, 1951; 8.
    - William Cahn to Milo Lathrop Regarding Radio Broadcasts, April 10, 1947; 9.
    - Cahn to Lathrom Regarding Publicity, March 10, 1949; 10.
    - Cahn to Janet Scott Regarding Publicity, March 14, 1949; 11.
    - James Carey to William Turnbull Regarding Labor History, March 12, 1940; 12.
    - Carey to Turnbull, March 30, 1940; 13.
    - Steve DiSiena to Phil Regarding Unemployment and Political Action, 14.
    - Emspak to Turnbull Regarding New York Power and Light Organization with March 16, 1937, William Connor Letter to J L. Lewis, March 24, 1937, Lewis Secretary Letter to Connor, April 5, 1937, John Brophy Letter to Connor and Emspak Letter to Connor, April 7, 1937; 15.
    - Emspak to August Hein Regarding Supplies, April 9, 1937; 16.
    - Emspak to Turnbull Regarding Finances, May 25, 1937; 17.
  - District 3 Incoming Correspondence, July 6, 1937-June 12, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Julius Emspak to August Hein Regarding Locals 508 and 511, July 6, 1937; 1.
    - Emspak to William Turnbull Regarding Finances, March 23, 1938; 2.
    - Emspak to Turnbull Regarding Philadelphia Organization, May 4, 1938; 3.
    - Emspak to Frank Bloom Regarding Finances, May 11, 1938; 4.
    - Emspak to Almond Clough Regarding Mailing List, August 12, 1941; 5.
    - Emspak to Donald Smith Regarding Mine, Mill and Smelter Strikes, February 24, 1942; 6.
    - Emspak to Emmanuel Fried Regarding Black Workers with List, September 21, 1942; 7.
    - Emspak to Harriet Warren Regarding Finances, January 11, 1943; 8.
    - Emspak to Fried Regrading UE News, February 2, 1943; 9.
    - Emspak to Ted Buczek Regarding Staff Finances, March 16, 1943; 10.
    - Emspak to General Vice Presidents Regarding Political Action, July 21, 1943; 11.
    - Emspak to Buczek Regarding Jamestown Metal Equipment Organization, October 25, 1943; 12.
    - Emspak to Buczek Regarding Conscription, March 8, 1944; 13.
    - Emspak to Buczek Regarding Staff Members and Military Personnel, April 3, 1944; 14.
    - Emspak Telegram to Philomena DeSiena, April 30, 1945; 15.
    - Emspak to General Executive Board Members Regarding Veterans and Dues with Emspak Letter to UE Locals, June 12, 1945; 16.
    - Emspak to A. Anderson Regarding Finances, August 7, 1945; 17.
    - Emspak Telegram to Edward Landy, October 2, 1945; 18.
    - Emspak to Anderson Regarding Finances, October 4, 1945; 19.
    - Emspak to Lyle Cordnier Regarding Wages and United Coke, Glas and Chemical with October, 22, 1945, Emspak Telegram to Charles Doyle and Octobe 19, 1945, Doyle Telegram to Emspak, October 23, 1945; 20.
    - Emspak to John Baston Regarding Political Action Committee, November 7, 1945; 21.
  - District 3 Incoming Correspondence, August 12, 1937-July 16, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Julius Emspak to John Baston Regarding Finances, January 18, 1946; 1.
    - Emspak to Baston Regarding Political Action Committee, May 8, 1946; 2.
    - Emspak to Emanuel Fried Regarding Charles Cooper Memorial, February 17, 1947; 3.
    - Emspak to Fried Regarding Finances and Constitution, May 8, 1948; 4.
    - Emspak to Jerold Mooney Regarding 1948 UE Convention, March 31, 1948; 5.
    - Emspak to Leon Novak Regarding Finances, December 9, 1949; 6.
    - Emspak to Mooney Regarding Local 203 and Factionalism, January 25, 1950; 7.
    - Emspak to Mooney Regarding Finances, February 15, 1950; 8.
    - Emspak to Novak Regarding Local 301 and Finances with April 10, 1950, Novak Letter to Emspak and April 10, 1950, Form, April 12, 1950; 9.
    - Emspak Telegram to Hotel Mark Twain, October 22, 1951; 10.
    - Emspak to Eugene Tooke Regarding Membership with Results, July 16, 1953; 11.
    - Albert Fitzgerald to Harold Buck Regarding Michael Jimenez Banqet, April 25, 1951; 12.
    - Nat Geller to Ted Buczek Regarding Staff Finances, October 16, 1942; 13.
    - Clifford McAvoy to Milo Lathrop, February 13, 1947; 14.
    - James Matles to Dorothy Loes, August 12, 1937; 15.
    - Matles to Donald Smith Regarding District 3 and Staff Members, October 23, 1941; 16.
    - Matles to Smith Regarding District 3, February 16, 1942; 17.
    - Matles to Emanuel Fried Regarding Mailing List, October 27, 1942; 18.
    - Matles to Ted Buczk Regarding Overtime, November 6, 1942; 19.
    - Matles to Buczek Regarding Supplies, March 10, 1943; 20.
    - Matles to Buczek Regarding Staff Members, May 10, 1943; 21.
    - Matles to Al Clough Regarding Westinghouse White Collar Workers, July 8, 1943; 22.
  - District 3 Incoming Correspondence, June 22, 1943-April 27, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - James Matles to Al Clough Regarding Staff Members, and Rochester, Buffalo and Syracuse Organizations, November 12, 1945; 1.
    - Matles to Charles Cooper Regarding Staff Members, November 12, 1946; 2.
    - Matles to International Representatives Regarding Per Capita, January 25, 1954; 3.
    - Matles to Harris Dean Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry and Staff Members with David Ratner Memo, April 27, 1954; 4.
    - Matles to Jake Marachione Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry and Staff Members, April 27, 1954; 5.
    - Matles to Al Taft Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry and Staff Members, April 27, 1954; 6.
    - Matles to Gerald Tooke Regarding IUE inter-unoin Rivalry and Staff Members, April 27, 1954; 7.
    - Matles to Victor Telsch Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry and Staff Members, May 3, 1954; 8.
    - Matles to Raymond Metzinger Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry and Staff Members with June 8, 1954, Letter to Dave, June 9, 1954; 9.
    - Edward Mathews Letter Regarding Wages and Job Classification, June 22, 1943; 10.
    - James Mead Telegram to Leo Jandreau, June 13, 1944; 11.
    - David Ratner to Edmond Rice Regarding Finances, July 1, 1947; 12.
    - Ratner to Leon Novak Regarding Staff Finances, August 26, 1948; 13.
    - Ratner to Novak Regarding Bail Bond, April 17, 1950; 14.
  - District 3 Outgoing Correspondence, October 21, 1942-April 12, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Andrew Anderson to Julius Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, December 1, 1944; 1.
    - Anderson to Julius Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, July 18, 1945; 2.
    - Anderson to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, August 16, 1945; 3.
    - Anderson to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, August 16-October 1, 1945; 4-5.
    - John Baston to Emspak Regarding PAC, October 31, 1945; 6.
    - Baston to Emspak Regarding PAC, November 30-Decemer 31, 1945; 7-8.
    - Baston to Emspak Regarding PAC and Sparto Wire, April 12, 1946; 9.
    - Baston to Emspak Regarding PAC, May 3, 1946; 10.
    - Willard Bliss to Emspak Regarding Ilion, October 21, 1942; 11.
    - Bliss to Emspak Regarding Finances, February 22, 1943; 12.
    - Bliss to Emspak Regarding Military Presonnel, August 23, 1943; 13.
    - Bliss to Emspak Regarding New General Electric Plant, December 17, 1943; 14.
    - Bliss to Emspak Regarding Veterans and Finances, February 22, 1944; 15.
    - Bliss to Emspak Regarding Conscription and Staff Members, February 29, 1944; 16.
    - Bliss to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, August 31, 1944; 17.
  - District 3 Outgoing Correspondence, April 26, 1938-November 2, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Willard Bliss to Julius Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee with PAC Deduction Forms, November 2, 1944; 1.
    - Bliss to Clifford McAvoy Regarding Political Action, November 10, 1944; 2.
    - Frank Bloom to William Mitchell Regarding Political Action, April 26, 1938; 3.
    - Bloom to Emspak Regarding District 3 Officers, October 25-31, 1938; 4-5.